Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office. Knowledge Centre subject files, 1941-2002 RL.11467
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office. Knowledge Centre subject files
1941-2002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
RL.11467
60.0 Linear Feet
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. It is headquartered in New York. The London Office first opened in 1899. The Knowledge Centre was a reference library for staff use. Collection comprises a vertical file of articles, clippings, market research reports, institutional and government publications and other printed material. Topics include advertising industry, alcoholic and non-alcoholic beverages, automobiles, computers and computer software, food, radio and television, tobacco products and travel and tourism industry. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Arranged numerically by index code.
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. It is headquartered in New York. The London Office first opened in 1899. The Knowledge Centre was a reference library for staff use.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office. Knowledge Centre subject files were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2008.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections: J. Walter Thompson Company Marketing vertical files; J. Walter Thompson Company Advertising vertical files; J. Walter Thompson Company Information Center vertical files; McCann-Erickson vertical files; McGraw-Hill Marketing Information Center vertical files.
Collection Overview
Collection comprises a vertical file of articles, clippings, market research reports, institutional and government publications and other printed material. Topics include advertising industry, alcoholic and non-alcoholic beverages, automobiles, computers and computer software, food, radio and television, tobacco products and travel and tourism industry. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising; Advertising agencies -- Great Britain; Marketing research; Advertising, Outdoor; Alcoholic beverage industry; Television advertising; Travel; Tourism -- Europe; Tobacco; Food -- Marketing; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
- Knowledge Centre Subject Files, 1941-2002; 1
  - 178.6 Alcohol Use, 1977-1999; 8 folders (Box 1)
  - 178.6 Alcohol Use, 1977-1999; 2 folders (Box OV1)
  - 312.5 Marriage, 1980-2000; 6 folders (Box 1)
  - 323.3 Social Classes, 1963-1999; 4 folders (Box 1)
  - 325.1 Immigration and Immigrants, 1986-2000; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 325.2 Emigration, 1976-1996; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 330.941 Recession, 1980-1999; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - 330.943 Economic--General, 1979-1999; 8 folders (Box 2)
  - 330.943 Economic--General, 1979-1999; 4 folders (Box OV1)
  - 330.944 Millennium, 1994-2000; 3 folders (Box 2)
  - 330.944 Millennium, 1994-2000; 2 folders (Box OV1)
  - 331.4 Employment of Women, 1988-2000; 4 folders (Box 2)
  - 331.41 Women--Sex Equality, 1984-1999; 3 folders (Box 2)
  - 339.49 Environment, "Green" concept, 1989-1999; 3 folders (Box 3)
  - 339.491 Conservation, 1992-1999; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - 339.491 Conservation, 1992-1999 (Box OV1)
  - 380.1622 Nationalized Industries, 1983-1995 (Box 3)
  - 380.1623 Privatisation and Nationalisation, 1980-2000; 10 folders (Box 3)
  - 383.3 Telecommunications, 1990-2001; 7 folders (Box 3)
  - 383.3 Telecommunications, 1990-2001; 3 folders (Box OV2)
  - 383.4 Telephones, 1991-2001; 6 folders (Box 4)
  - 383.4 Telephones, 1991-2001 (Box OV2)
  - 383.5 Telephone Selling, 1979-1998; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - 383.5 Telephone Selling, 1979-1998 (Box OV2)
  - 385 Railways, 1980-1998; 3 folders (Box 4)
  - 385 Railways, 1980-1998 (Box OV3)
  - 389.1 Weights and Measures, 1962-1969 (Box 4)
  - 389.2 Metrication (conversion to metric system), 1965-1978; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - 389.2 Metrication (conversion to metric system), 1965-1978 (Box OV3)
  - 389.3 Decimal Currency Board, 1965-1971 (Box 4)
  - 610 Medicine--General, 1975-2000; 3 folders (Box 4)
  - 610 Medicine--General, 1975-2000 (Box OV3)
  - 610.69 Doctors and Nurses, 1963-1996; 3 folders (Box 4)
  - 612.39 Nutrition--General, 1982-1998; 3 folders (Box 5)
  - 612.399 Vitamins, 1984-1998; 3 folders (Box 5)
  - 612.65 Height and Weight, 1966-2001; 3 folders (Box 5)
  - 613.24 Slimming Diets, 1991-2000; 3 folders (Box 5)
  - 613.4 Baths and Bathing, 1980-2000; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - 613.78 Sleep, 1962-1999; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - 613.78 Sleep, 1962-1999 (Box OV3)
  - 614 Public Health, 1963-2000; 4 folders (Box 5)
  - 614 Public Health, 1963-2000 (Box OV3)
  - 614.05 Health Market, 1980-1998; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - 614.2 National Health Service, 1983-1999; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - 614.2 National Health Service, 1983-1999 (Box OV3)
  - 614.200 Private Health Insurance, 1980-2000; 8 folders (Box 6)
  - 614.2001 Private Health Insurance, 1980-2000; 3 folders (Box OV3)
  - 614.202 Mental Health, 1975-1999; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - 614.202 Mental Health, 1975-1999 (Box OV3)
  - 614.3 Food Hygiene and Food Poisoning, 1965-1998; 4 folders (Box 6)
  - 614.3 Food Hygiene and Food Poisoning, 1965-1998 (Box OV3)
  - 614.7 Pollution, 1987-1997; 5 folders (Box 6)
  - 614.7 Pollution, 1987-1997 (Box OV3)
  - 615 Drugs (Pharmaceutical), 1988-1996; 3 folders (Box 6)
  - 615 Drugs (Pharmaceutical), 1988-1996 (Box OV4)
  - 615.1 Over-the-Counter (OTC) Medicines, 1978-1999 (Box OV4)
  - 615.1 Over-the-Counter (OTC) Medicines, 1978-1999 (Box 6)
  - 615.783 Aspirin etc., 1986-1998; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - 615.783 Aspirin etc., 1986-1998 (Box OV4)
  - 621.3841 Radio, 1980-1999 (Box 7)
  - 621.3841 Radio, 1980-1999 (Box OV4)
  - 621.3846 BBC, 1984-1999; 5 folders (Box 7)
  - 621.3846 BBC, 1984-1999 (Box OV4)
  - 621.3847 BBC Attitudes to Advertising, 1985-1995 (Box 7)
  - 621.3848 Reith Lectures, 1979-1983 (Box 7)
  - 621.3882 Television Broadcasting, 1988-2001; 4 folders (Box 7)
  - 621.3882 Television Broadcasting, 1988-2001 (Box OV4)
  - 629.2 Motor Industry, 1959-1999; 6 folders (Box 7)
  - 629.2 Motor Industry, 1959-1999; 3 folders (Box OV4)
  - 629.21 Motor Industry Statistics, 1980-1986 (Box 7)
  - 629.22 Car Parts, 1987-1998 (Box 7)
  - 629.22 Car Parts, 1987-1998 (Box OV4)
  - 629.222 Motor Cars, 1992-1999; 5 folders (Box 8)
  - 629.222 Motor Cars, 1992-1999; 4 folders (Box OV5)
  - 629.2221 Taxicabs, 1987-1993 (Box 8)
  - 629.2222 Electric Vehicles, 1981-1994 (Box 8)
  - 629.2222 Electric Vehicles, 1981-1994 (Box OV5)
  - 629.223 Trucks, 1994-1999 (Box 8)
  - 629.223 Trucks, 1994-1999 (Box OV5)
  - 629.2272 Bicycles, Mopeds, etc., 1981-1998; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - 629.2275 Motorcycles, 1982-1999; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - 629.2275 Motorcycles, 1982-1999 (Box OV5)
  - 629.2486 Tires, 1990-1996 (Box 8)
  - 629.2486 Tires, 1990-1996 (Box OV5)
  - 629.25 Internal Combustion Engines, 1993-1994 (Box 8)
  - 629.25 Internal Combustion Engines, 1993-1994 (Box OV5)
  - 629.27 Car Accessories, 1983-1996; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - 629.281 Motoring, 1982-1999; 3 folders (Box 8)
  - 629.281 Motoring, 1982-1999 (Box OV5)
  - 629.282 Motor Racing, 1973-1997; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - 629.282 Motor Racing, 1973-1997 (Box OV6)
  - 629.283 Car Hire, Fleet Cars, Rentals, Leasing, 1984-1998 (Box 8)
  - 629.283 Car Hire, Fleet Cars, Rentals, Leasing, 1984-1998 (Box OV6)
  - 629.285 Garages, 1986-2002; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - 629.285 Garages, 1986-2002 (Box OV6)
  - 633.34 Soya Beans, 1971-1983; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - 633.36 Peanuts/Nuts, 1961-1997; 3 folders (Box 9)
  - 633.6 Sugar, 1969-1997; 3 folders (Box 9)
  - 633.65 Artificial Sweeteners, 1973-1997; 3 folders (Box 9)
  - 634 Fruit, 1988-1999; 3 folders (Box 9)
  - 634 Fruit, 1988-1999 (Box OV6)
  - 634.11 Apples, 1972-1998 (Box 9)
  - 634.11 Apples, 1972-1998 (Box OV6)
  - 635 Vegetables, 1983-2001; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - 635 Vegetables, 1983-2001 (Box OV6)
  - 635.21 Potatoes, 1981-1998; 3 folders (Box 9)
  - 636.4132 Pork, Ham and Bacon, 1986-1999 (Box 9)
  - 636.4132 Pork, Ham and Bacon, 1986-1999 (Box OV6)
  - 636.5 Poultry and Poultry Foods, 1986-1997 (Box 9)
  - 637 Dairy Products, 1987-1995; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - 639.2 Fish and Fishing Industry, 1984-1999; 3 folders (Box 10)
  - 639.2 Fish and Fishing Industry, 1984-1999 (Box OV6)
  - 641 Cooking, 1971-2000; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - 641.36 Meat, 1979-2000; 5 folders (Box 10)
  - 641.36 Meat, 1979-2000 (Box OV6)
  - 641.38 Sausages, 1967-1995; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - 641.38 Sausages, 1967-1995 (Box OV6)
  - 641.83 Salads, 1971-1994; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - 642.11 Breakfasts, 1962-1999; 3 folders (Box 10)
  - 642.11 Breakfasts, 1962-1999 (Box OV6)
  - 643 Home--Bathroom, 1971-1995; 3 folders (Box 10)
  - 643 Home--Bathroom, 1971-1995 (Box OV6)
  - 643.2 Domestic Appliances, 1987-1997 (Box 10)
  - 643.2 Domestic Appliances, 1987-1997 (Box OV6)
  - 643.24 Electrical Appliances, 1978-1999; 6 folders (Box 11)
  - 643.24 Electrical Appliances, 1978-1999 (Box OV6)
  - 643.241 White Goods, 1983-2000 (Box 11)
  - 643.2411 Cookers (including Microwave Ovens), 1980-1996; 3 folders (Box 11)
  - 643.2411 Cookers (including Microwave Ovens), 1980-1996 (Box OV6)
  - 643.2412 Dishwashers, 1972-1996 (Box 11)
  - 643.2412 Dishwashers, 1972-1996 (Box OV6)
  - 643.2413 Refrigerators/Freezers, 1976-1998; 3 folders (Box 11)
  - 643.2414 Vacuum Cleaners, 1967-1997; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - 643.2414 Vacuum Cleaners, 1967-1997 (Box OV6)
  - 643.242 Small Electrical Appliances, 1976-1997; 3 folders (Box 11)
  - 643.2421 Food Mixers, 1980-1996; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - 643.3 Cookware, 1983-1998 (Box 12)
  - 643.31 Kitchens and Kitchen Furniture, 1982-1999 (Box 12)
  - 643.32 Kitchen Utensils, 1973-1999 (Box 12)
  - 643.33 Kitchen Wraps, 1979-1993 (Box 12)
  - 644.1 Central/Domestic Heating, 1976-1997; 3 folders (Box 12)
  - 644.1 Central/Domestic Heating, 1976-1997 (Box OV7)
  - 644.3 Domestic Lighting, 1966-1999 (Box 12)
  - 644.3 Domestic Lighting, 1966-1999; 2 folders (Box OV7)
  - 647.9 Catering (includes school lunches), 1987-1999; 3 folders (Box 12)
  - 647.9 Catering (includes school lunches), 1987-1999; 2 folders (Box OV7)
  - 647.94 Hotels, 1980-1998; 3 folders (Box 12)
  - 647.94 Hotels, 1980-1998 (Box OV7)
  - 647.941 Inns and Public Houses, 1986-1996; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - 647.941 Inns and Public Houses, 1986-1996; 2 folders (Box OV7)
  - 647.95 Eating Out, 1965-1999; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - 647.95 Eating Out, 1965-1999 (Box OV7)
  - 648.1 Washing, 1960-1996 (Box 13)
  - 648.1 Washing, 1960-1996; 2 folders (Box OV7)
  - 648.18 Launderettes, 1949-1994 (Box 13)
  - 648.18 Launderettes, 1949-1994 (Box OV7)
  - 648.24 Washing Machines, 1964-1996 (Box 13)
  - 658.8 Marketing, 1983-2001; 5 folders (Box 13)
  - 658.8 Marketing, 1983-2001; 2 folders (Box OV7)
  - 658.813 Export Marketing, 1988-1997; 3 folders (Box 13)
  - 658.816 Capital Goods Market, 1969-1996 (Box 13)
  - 658.816 Capital Goods Market, 1969-1996 (Box OV7)
  - 658.8177 Luxury Goods Market, 1986-2000; 3 folders (Box 13)
  - 658.8177 Luxury Goods Market, 1986-2000 (Box OV7)
  - 658.82 Sales Management, 1969-1999; 3 folders (Box 13)
  - 658.82 Sales Management, 1969-1999 (Box OV7)
  - 658.8713 Furniture Retailing, 1979-1998; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - 658.8713 Furniture Retailing, 1979-1998; 2 folders (Box OV8)
  - 658.872 Department Stores, 1980-2000; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - 658.872 Department Stores, 1980-2000; 2 folders (Box OV8)
  - 658.873 Co-Operative Societies, 1964-1997 (Box 14)
  - 658.873 Co-Operative Societies, 1964-1997; 2 folders (Box OV8)
  - 658.874 Chain Stores, 1982-1997 (Box 14)
  - 658.874 Chain Stores, 1982-1997; 2 folders (Box OV8)
  - 658.875 Independent Retailers, 1987-1998 (Box 14)
  - 658.875 Independent Retailers, 1987-1998 (Box OV8)
  - 658.8751 Grocery Trade, 1987-2000; 3 folders (Box 14)
  - 658.8751 Grocery Trade, 1987-2000; 2 folders (Box OV8)
  - 658.8756 Chemists (Pharmacists), 1972-1999 (Box 14)
  - 658.8756 Chemists (Pharmacists), 1972-1999 (Box OV8)
  - 658.8765 Self-Service, 1991-2000; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 658.8765 Self-Service, 1991-2000; 2 folders (Box OV8)
  - 658.8766 Discount Stores, 1975-2000; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 658.8766 Discount Stores, 1975-2000; 2 folders (Box OV8)
  - 658.877 Automatic Vending Machines, 1962-1997; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 658.877 Automatic Vending Machines, 1962-1997 (Box OV8)
  - 658.878 Mobile Shops and Street Markets, 1967-1997 (Box 14)
  - 658.878 Mobile Shops and Street Markets, 1967-1997 (Box OV8)
  - 658.879 Shopping Centers, 1989-2000 (Box 14)
  - 658.879 Shopping Centers, 1989-2000; 2 folders (Box OV8)
  - 658.883 Hire Purchase, 1979-1987; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 658.884 Mail Order, 1979-1997; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 658.884 Mail Order, 1979-1997; 2 folders (Box OV8)
  - 659 Advertising--General, 1963-2001; 5 folders (Box 15)
  - 659 Advertising--General, 1963-2001; 2 folders (Box OV8)
  - 659.00037 Advertising Law, 1963-2000; 5 folders (Box 15)
  - 659.00037 Advertising Law, 1963-2000; 2 folders (Box OV9)
  - 659.002 Advertising Expenditure, 1960-1999; 6 folders (Box 15)
  - 659.002 Advertising Expenditure, 1960-1999; 2 folders (Box OV9)
  - 659.003 Economic Effects of Advertising, 1976-1999; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - 659.003 Economic Effects of Advertising, 1976-1999 (Box OV9)
  - 659.013 Criticism of Advertising, 1961-2000; 4 folders (Box 16)
  - 659.013 Criticism of Advertising, 1961-2000; 2 folders (Box OV9)
  - 659.015 Psychology of Advertising, 1958-1995 (Box 16)
  - 659.015 Psychology of Advertising, 1958-1995 (Box OV9)
  - 659.0157 Subliminal Advertising, 1958-1997 (Box 16)
  - 659.0157 Subliminal Advertising, 1958-1997 (Box OV9)
  - 659.062 Advertising Associations and Clubs, 1982-1997; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - 659.062 Advertising Associations and Clubs, 1982-1997 (Box OV9)
  - 659.068 Advertising Ethics, 1989-1999; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - 659.068 Advertising Ethics, 1989-1999; 2 folders (Box OV9)
  - 659.068 Advertising Standard Authority (ASA), 1980-1999 (Box 16)
  - 659.068 Advertising Standard Authority (ASA), 1980-1999 (Box OV9)
  - 659.0682 Codes of Advertising Practice, 1980-2000; 3 folders (Box 16)
  - 659.0682 Codes of Advertising Practice, 1980-2000 (Box OV9)
  - 659.069 Advertising Careers, 1985-1997 (Box 16)
  - 659.069 Advertising Careers, 1985-1997; 2 folders (Box OV9)
  - 659.07 Advertising Education, 1966-1997; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - 659.07 Advertising Education, 1966-1997 (Box OV9)
  - 659.11 Public Relations, 1994-1998 (Box 17)
  - 659.11 Public Relations, 1994-1998 (Box OV9)
  - 659.1121 Company Reports, 1962-1999 (Box 17)
  - 659.1121 Company Reports, 1962-1999 (Box OV10)
  - 659.1122 Financial Services Advertising, 1981-1998; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - 659.1122 Financial Services Advertising, 1981-1998 (Box OV10)
  - 659.14 Sponsorship, 1988-2000; 4 folders (Box 17)
  - 659.14 Sponsorship, 1988-2000; 2 folders (Box OV10)
  - 659.21 Government Advertising and Public Relations, 1983-1997 (Box 17)
  - 659.21 Government Advertising and Public Relations, 1983-1997 (Box OV10)
  - 659.211 Central Office of Information, 1987-197 (Box 17)
  - 659.211 Central Office of Information, 1987-197 (Box OV10)
  - 659.22 Corporate Image, 1984-2001; 5 folders (Box 17)
  - 659.22 Corporate Image, 1984-2001; 2 folders (Box OV10)
  - 659.235 Classified Advertising, 1971-1998; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - 659.235 Classified Advertising, 1971-1998 (Box OV10)
  - 659.24 Co-operative Advertising, 1981-1983 (Box 17)
  - 659.25 Technical and Industrial Advertising, 1970-2000; 3 folders (Box 17)
  - 659.25 Technical and Industrial Advertising, 1970-2000 (Box OV10)
  - 659.3 Advertising Agencies--General, 1983-2000; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - 659.3 Advertising Agencies--General, 1983-2000; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - 659.3 Advertising Agencies--General, 1983-2000; 3 folders (Box OV10)
  - 659.305 Abbott Mead Vickers, 1983-1997 (Box 18)
  - 659.305 Abbott Mead Vickers, 1983-1997 (Box OV11)
  - 659.305 Backer Spielvogel Bates, 1988 (Box 18)
  - 659.305 CIA Media, 1997 (Box 18)
  - 659.305 Grey Advertising, 1966-1998 (Box 18)
  - 659.305 Grey Advertising, 1966-1998 (Box OV11)
  - 659.305 Leo Burnett, 1969-1995; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - 659.305 Leo Burnett, 1969-1995 (Box OV11)
  - 659.305 Lowe Howard Spink, 1981-1993; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - 659.305 Lowe Howard Spink, 1981-1993 (Box OV11)
  - 659.305 McCann-Erickson, 1981-1996; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - 659.305 McCann-Erickson, 1981-1996 (Box OV11)
  - 659.305 Olgivy & Mather, 1975-1998; 3 folders (Box 18)
  - 659.305 Olgivy & Mather, 1975-1998 (Box OV11)
  - 659.305 Publicis, 1966-1997 (Box 18)
  - 659.305 Publicis, 1966-1997 (Box OV11)
  - 659.305 Saatchi & Saatchi, 1986-1995; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - 659.305 Saatchi & Saatchi, 1986-1995; 2 folders (Box OV11)
  - 659.305 Ted Bates, 1978-1985 (Box 18)
  - 659.305 Ted Bates, 1978-1985 (Box OV11)
  - 659.305 WCRS (Wright Collins Scott Rutherford), 1979-1999 (Box 18)
  - 659.305 WCRS (Wright Collins Scott Rutherford), 1979-1999 (Box OV11)
  - 659.305 Young & Rubicam, 1986-1998 (Box 18)
  - 659.305 Young & Rubicam, 1986-1998 (Box OV11)
  - 659.3051 D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles (DMBB) (also Benton & Bowles; D'Arcy MacManus Masius), 1973-1998 (Box 18)
  - 659.3051 D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles (DMBB) (also Benton & Bowles; D'Arcy MacManus Masius), 1973-1998 (Box OV11)
  - 659.3051 Saatchi/Cordiant, 1995-1999; 4 folders (Box 19)
  - 659.306 Media Independents, 1981-1997 (Box 19)
  - 659.306 Media Independents, 1981-1997 (Box OV11)
  - 659.31 Choosing an Agency, 1965-1996 (Box 19)
  - 659.31 Choosing an Agency, 1965-1996 (Box OV11)
  - 659.32 Client-Agency Relations, 1963-1998; 8 folders (Box 19)
  - 659.32 Client-Agency Relations, 1963-1998 (Box OV11)
  - 659.33 Agency Administration, 1962-1995 (Box 19)
  - 659.33 Agency Administration, 1962-1995 (Box OV12)
  - 659.332 Agency Staff, 1984-2000 (Box 19)
  - 659.332 Agency Staff, 1984-2000 (Box OV12)
  - 659.333 Account Planning, 1980-1998 (Box 19)
  - 659.333 Account Planning, 1980-1998 (Box OV12)
  - 659.334 Agency Accounting, 1970-2001; 3 folders (Box 19)
  - 659.334 Agency Accounting, 1970-2001 (Box OV12)
  - 659.3344 Agency Billings, 1957-1992; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - 659.3344 Agency Billings, 1957-1992 (Box OV12)
  - 659.41 Agency Solicitation, 1967-1999 (Box 20)
  - 659.41 Agency Solicitation, 1967-1999 (Box OV12)
  - 659.43 Ad Appropriation, 1970-1999; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - 659.43 Ad Appropriation, 1970-1999 (Box OV12)
  - 659.44 Advertising-Sales Ratio, 1979-1998 (Box 20)
  - 659.5 Advertising--Creative Aspects, 1962-2001; 3 folders (Box 20)
  - 659.5 Advertising--Creative Aspects, 1962-2001; 3 folders (Box OV12)
  - 659.5 Advertising--Creative Aspects--Coca-Cola Case Study, 1991-1993; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - 659.51 Advertising--Music and Jingles, 1976-2001; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - 659.51 Advertising--Music and Jingles, 1976-2001; 2 folders (Box OV13)
  - 659.513 Humor in Advertising, 1971-1999 (Box 20)
  - 659.513 Humor in Advertising, 1971-1999 (Box OV13)
  - 659.5135 Advertising Cartoons, 1974-1993; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - 659.5135 Advertising Cartoons, 1974-1993 (Box OV13)
  - 659.52 Copy Writing and Copywriters, 1965-1998; 3 folders (Box 20)
  - 659.52 Copy Writing and Copywriters, 1965-1998; 2 folders (Box OV13)
  - 659.526 Copy Testing, 1941-1999 (Box 20)
  - 659.526 Copy Testing, 1941-1999 (Box OV13)
  - 659.53 Advertising Art, 1980-1998 (Box 20)
  - 659.53 Advertising Art, 1980-1998 (Box OV13)
  - 659.6 Media, 1991-2001; 5 folders (Box 21)
  - 659.6 Media, 1991-2001; 3 folders (Box OV13)
  - 659.601 International Media, 1979-1997 (Box 21)
  - 659.601 International Media, 1979-1997; 2 folders (Box OV13)
  - 659.61 Media Selection, 1963-2001; 5 folders (Box 21)
  - 659.61 Media Selection (includes Interactive), 1963-2001; 3 folders (Box OV13)
  - 659.615 Media Rates, 1976-1997; 2 folders (Box 21)
  - 659.615 Media Rates, 1976-1997 (Box OV13)
  - 659.617 Media Research, 1969-2000; 5 folders (Box 21)
  - 659.617 Media Research, 1969-2000 (Box OV13)
  - 659.62 Press, 1990-1998 (Box 21)
  - 659.62 Press, 1990-1998 (Box OV14)
  - 659.621 Newspapers and Comics, 1988-2000; 2 folders (Box 21)
  - 659.621 Newspapers and Comics, 1988-2000; 2 folders (Box OV14)
  - 659.6221 Magazines, 1992-2000; 4 folders (Box 22)
  - 659.6221 Magazines, 1992-2000 (Box OV14)
  - 659.6221 Magazines--Profiles of Cosmopolitan, Good Housekeeping, 1997 (Box OV14)
  - 659.641 Direct Mail/Direct Response, 1990-2000; 9 folders (Box 22)
  - 659.641 Direct Mail/Direct Response (includes DRTV), 1990-2000; 5 folders (Box OV14)
  - 659.643 Outdoor Advertising, 1967-1999; 4 folders (Box 22)
  - 659.643 Outdoor Advertising, 1967-1999 (Box OV15)
  - 659.65 Cinema Advertising, 1960-1998; 3 folders (Box 22)
  - 659.65 Cinema Advertising, 1960-1998 (Box OV15)
  - 659.66 Radio--Audience and Research, 1989-2001; 3 folders (Box 22)
  - 659.66 Radio--Audience and Research, 1989-2001 (Box OV15)
  - 659.67 Commercial Television and TV Companies, 1995-2000 (Box 23)
  - 659.67 Commercial Television and TV Companies, 1995-2000 (Box OV15)
  - 659.67003 Television Advertising Expenditure and Revenue, 1969-1999; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - 659.67003 Television Advertising Expenditure and Revenue, 1969-1999 (Box OV15)
  - 659.6706 Independent Broadcasting Authority, 1979-1998; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - 659.6706 Independent Broadcasting Authority, 1979-1998; 2 folders (Box OV15)
  - 659.67063 Breakfast Television, 1979-1993; 3 folders (Box 23)
  - 659.67063 Breakfast Television, 1979-1993; 2 folders (Box OV15)
  - 659.67065 ITV (Independent Television) Companies, 1953-1995; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - 659.67065 ITV (Independent Television) Companies, 1953-1995; 2 folders (Box OV15)
  - 659.67072 Television Audience Research, 1984-2000; 4 folders (Box 23)
  - 659.67072 Television Audience Research, 1984-2000 (Box OV15)
  - 659.672 Television Programmes, 1986-2000; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - 659.672 Television Programmes, 1986-2000; 2 folders (Box OV15)
  - 659.6721 Television Commercials, 1985-2001; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - 659.6721 Television Commercials, 1985-2001; 2 folders (Box OV15)
  - 659.6722 Animals in Advertising, 1985-1994 (Box 23)
  - 659.6722 Animals in Advertising, 1985-1994 (Box OV15)
  - 659.7 Merchandising General, 1971-1999 (Box 23)
  - 659.7 Merchandising General, 1971-1999 (Box OV15)
  - 659.701 Character Merchandising, 1984-1999; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - 659.701 Character Merchandising, 1984-1999 (Box OV15)
  - 659.702 Brand Diversification, 1983-2001; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - 659.702 Brand Diversification, 1983-2001 (Box OV15)
  - 659.715 Competitions, 1971-1987 (Box 24)
  - 659.715 Competitions, 1971-1987 (Box OV15)
  - 659.72 Sales Promotion, 1986-2001; 4 folders (Box 24)
  - 659.72 Sales Promotion, 1986-2001; 3 folders (Box OV16)
  - 659.72 Sales Promotion--Carlsburg World Cup case study, 1990 (Box 24)
  - 659.726 Coupon Offers, 1984-1998 (Box 24)
  - 659.726 Coupon Offers, 1984-1998 (Box OV16)
  - 659.727 Gift Buying, 1967-1999; 2 folders (Box 24)